{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Register of disbursing oﬃcers shall be maintained in Form Number _______",
      "correct_answer": "TR 111",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        " TR 105",
        " TR 110,
        "TR 112"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A Register in Form ______ shall be maintained at the Sub Treasuries for noting details of passed bills for payment.",
      "correct_answer": "TR 18",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TR 7A",
        "TR 12",
        "TR 21
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The Treasury Register of personal deposits is in form",
      "correct_answer": "TA 15",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        " TA 13",
        " TA 12",
        "TA 11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "_______ Deposit shall never be repaid in past.",
      "correct_answer": "Earnest money deposit",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security deposit ",
        "Civil Court deposit",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A serially numbered currency chest slip should be maintained in which of the following forms?",
      "correct_answer": "TR 38",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TR 37",
        "TR 39",
        "TR 40"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "No TSB account will be transferred during the month of March specify the rule.",
      "correct_answer": "TSB Rule 32",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TSB Rule 33",
        "TSB Rule 34",
        "TSB Rule 35"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who is responsible for maintaining the required form of currency chests?",
      "correct_answer": "Currency oﬃcer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Director of Treasuries",
        " District Treasury oﬃcer",
        "None of these "
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which is the rule for TSB Account opened in the name of minor should not be transferred after the minor attaining maturity?",
      "correct_answer": "TSB Rule 35",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TSB Rule 34",
        "TSB Rule 32",
        "TSB Rule 31"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A cheque means",
      "correct_answer": "written order",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "request",
        "submission",
        "letter"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Statement of lapsed deposit is",
      "correct_answer": " TA 36",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TA 38",
        "TA 35,
        "TA 31"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
